popundertotal.com 2019-06-06

# Privacy Policy

Storm Digital Company (PopUnderTOTAL) provides advertising technology solutions ("Technology") that enables media companies, online advertisers, and web publishers to buy, sell, and measure the the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns. This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") explains how personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by PopUnderTOTAL with respect to your use of the websites located at http://PopUnderTOTAL.com (the "Site") and how personal information is collected, used, and processed through the Technology on behalf of the online advertisers, publishers, business partners, and other businesses that use PopUnderTOTAL's services ("Clients").

Use of the terms "we" and "us" in this Privacy Policy means PopUnderTOTAL. Capitalized words not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning as defined in the Terms. By using the Site, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

### Information about the Site

Your privacy is important to us, and our policy is simple: we will collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Site unless you choose to provide that information (as explained further below). This Privacy Policy does not describe information collection practices on other sites, including those linked to or from the Site.

PopUnderTOTAL may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a revised Privacy Policy on the Site, and/or sending information regarding the amendment to the email address you provide to PopUnderTOTAL. You are responsible for regularly reviewing the Site to obtain timely notice of such amendments. You shall be deemed to have accepted such amendments by continuing your use of the Site or of your Account after such amendments have been posted or information about such amendments has been sent to you.

**Commitment to Privacy**

The European Union ("EU") maintains strict privacy laws through General Data Privacy Regulation ("GDPR") and protecting our customer's data is a main concern to ensure that we maintain the required compliance with the governing authorities.

**Your Data Rights**

If you are in the EEA, you have a right to (subject to a limited number of exceptions):   
(i) request access to and rectification or erasure of your personal information;   
(ii) obtain restriction of processing or to object to processing of your personal information;   
and (iii) ask for a copy of your personal information to be provided to them, or a third party, in a digital format. You also have the right to lodge a complaint about the processing of your personal information with your local data protection authority in the EEA. 

If you are a client, and would like the personal information PopUnderTOTAL hold about you to be corrected or updated please contact info@popundertotal.com. 

For the deletion and erasure of personal information, email info@popundertotal.com to begin the process and we will respond to your request within 30 days.

**Normal Site Usage:**

You can visit many portions of the Site without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. Information we may collect from such a Site visit is the default information customarily logged by web server software, which may include the date and time of your visit, the originating IP address, and the pages and images requested. We may use this information to generate statistics and measure site activity to improve the usefulness of the Site to our visitors and Account holders.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information:**

In order to use certain functionality of the Site, including but not limited to buying and selling ads, you will need to create an Account and submit certain personal information. This information includes but is not limited to your name and contact information such as your postal address, telephone number and email address. When you create your Account, you will need to choose a password. If you are an advertiser, we need you to provide certain billing information, such as credit card, bank account or PayPal information. If you are a publisher of ads, we need you to provide information about your website and payment method, such as bank or PayPal account information.

PopUnderTOTAL will use your personal information to provide you with requested services and products, to set up and administer your Account, to reply to your inquiries, to improve the Site, our products and services, for internal research, analyses and fraud prevention, and to contact you regarding general company news, new products and services, and industry trends. We use your email address to inform advertisers about the performance of their ads and to inform publishers about any ads that they have sold. By applying for an Account and providing the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

When you use the Site, we may send one or more cookies (a small data file) to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including recognizing you as a previous visitor to the Site, to populate forms, to provide you with customized viewing options, and to maintain personalized services throughout the Site.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure:**

We may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on our behalf to provide products and services requested by you and to banks, processors, card associations, and other financial institutions and payment processors that are involved in the processing or screening of transactions applicable to your Account. We share personal information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information, however, we are not liable to you for any disclosure of your information made by such third parties.

Depending on the types of payment processing you choose with us, you may be required to or choose to have accounts directly with one or more of these third party providers, such as PayPal. Such third part providers' privacy policies apply for information provided to them.

Non-personally-identifiable information, and data in an aggregate form without disclosure of personally-identifiable information, may be provided to other parties for various business, marketing, and advertising uses, including but not limited to advertisers assessing the effectiveness of their ads.

We may also disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or if PopUnderTOTAL reasonably believes that such action is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process; (b) enforce the Terms; (c) respond to claims that any Content or Post violates the rights of third parties; (d) respond to your requests for customer service; or (e) protect the rights, property or personal safety of PopUnderTOTAL, Account holders, or any other party.

**Consent:**

If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not open an Account or provide any personal information to us. If you have provided personal information to us and cease to consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, you may update, modify or delete that information by clicking on the "Account details" link on the Site, logging in, and changing your Account information and settings as applicable. Please note that in order to provide our services to you, we need certain personal information for billing and payment purposes. If you delete certain information such as your name, email address, billing or mailing address or bank account information or credit card number, we will need to terminate your Account. If you require further assistance, please contact us at [ info@popundertotal.com](mailto:info@popundertotal.com) 

**Security:**

PopUnderTOTAL uses industry-standard data collection and encryption methodologies to ensure the secure collection and transmission of your personal information. We do not store any of your sensitive credit card information on our servers. While we try our best to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

### Information about the Technology

PopUnderTOTAL Technology may employ cookies to collect non-personally identifying information in the course of providing clients with ad-serving services and for the purpose of helping clients determine which advertisement is suitable to be delivered to a user. A cookie is a small text file that can be stored on a user's computer when that computer's browser views an advertisement or website of one of PopUnderTOTAL's clients. The cookie is associated with and unique to the specific computer. The cookie does not contain the user's name, address, phone number, email address, or anything that personally identifies it. PopUnderTOTAL collects into the cookie only non-personally identifying information such as the type of the computer's operating system, type of internet browser software, what web pages were viewed and at what time, and geographic location of user's internet service provider.

**Removing our 3rd party ad-serving cookie from your browser**

In your browser's settings, there should be an option to remove cookies. The domain that we set cookies during your use of PopUnderTOTAL Technology is popundertotal.com.
